Guide to the Willis "Tiny" Brown Papers, 1962-1989 IBT0071
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Willis "Tiny" Brown Papers
1966-1989
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Willis "Tiny" Brown
IBT0071
1 document boxes
Willis "Tiny" Brown was a Teamster truck driver from Peoria, Illinois. He was a regular participant in A,mmerican Trucking Association "roadeos" which were competitions that tested driving skills. The collection consists mainly of programs for the compeitions and the banquets that were the culmination of the competitions.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes postcards, event programs, labor booklets, and correspondence. The materials are dated from 1962 to 1989.
Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters [2015].
Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Collection: Willis "Tiny" Brown Papers. The collection is organized into one series: banquet programs and truck driving competition programs. It is arranged by type of program and then chronologically.
Biographical note
Willis "Tiny" Brown was a truck driver from Peoria, Illinois. He was a member of an Illinois IBT local, possibly Local 627, Peoria. In the 1950s and 1960s Willis Brown was a competitor in the annual state-level American Trucking Association "roadeos." tese competitons tested truckers' driving skills such as avoiding obstacles in the road, parking and backing out of a tight space. Willis Brown won a number of Illinois state championships and attending the national competions into the 1980s.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Trucking -- United States
- Willis "Tiny" Brown Papers, 1966-1989; Series 1 (Box 1)
  - Postcards, 1967-1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Banquet Program, 1965; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Banquet Program, 1966; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Banquet Program, 1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Banquet Program, 1971; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Banquet Program, 1972; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Banquet Program, 1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Banquet Program, 1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Competition Program, 1966; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Competition Program, 1969; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Competition Program, 1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Competition Program, 1971; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Competition Program, 1972; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Competition Program, 1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Competition Program, 1974; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Competition Program, 1975; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Competition Program, 1976; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Competition Program, 1977; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Competition Program, 1978; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Competition Program, 1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Competition Program, 1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Competition Program, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Competition Program, 1983; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Competition Program, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Competition Program, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Competition Program, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Competition Program, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Competition Program, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)